{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "It's heard that famous company will produce ___ it did last year.",
      "a": "20% more than T-shirts",
      "b": "more than 20% T-shirts",
      "c": "as many T-shirts 20% as",
      "d": "20% more T-shirts than",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Comparative: number + percent...+ more than....",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "9",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nobody can be ___ for the position than she is.",
      "a": "as fit",
      "b": "more fit",
      "c": "the more fit",
      "d": "more fitter",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": ".\n- More fit= fitter",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "9",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The opinions of the attendants proved ___ than we had expected.",
      "a": "as much valuable",
      "b": "far more valuable",
      "c": "a great deal of more valuable",
      "d": "slight more valuable",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Much/far/ rather/a little/a bit/ a lot + adj: to emphasize adj \n- Comparative: adj + er (short adj)/ more adj (long adj)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "9",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nancy is thought to be ___ her sister.",
      "a": "much pretty as",
      "b": "very pretty than",
      "c": "very much pretty than",
      "d": "much prettier than",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Much/far/ rather/a little/a bit/ a lot + adj: to emphasize adj \n- Comparative: adj + er (short adj)/ more adj (long adj) ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "9",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "This pair of boots is made of very good leather. It is much ___ expensive than the pair you bought yesterday.",
      "a": "little",
      "b": "too",
      "c": "most",
      "d": "less",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Much/far/ rather/a little/a bit/ a lot + adj: to emphasize adj \n- Comparison of Inferiority: Less + adj ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "9",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The lake in the west is far _________ than that in the east.",
      "a": "famouser",
      "b": "more famous",
      "c": "famous",
      "d": "the most famous",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Much/far/ rather/a little/a bit/ a lot + adj: to emphasize adj \n- Comparative: adj + er (short adj)/ more adj (long adj) ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "9",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Joseph, born in a rich family, has never had a ___ day.",
      "a": "most terrifying",
      "b": "more terrify",
      "c": "most terrified",
      "d": "more terrifying",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Comparative: used when comparing two things \n+ adj + er (short adj)/ more + adj (long adj) ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "9",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "How did you find your visit to the workshop? \"I thoroughly enjoyed it. It was ___ than I expected.\"",
      "a": "even much interesting",
      "b": "far more interesting",
      "c": "a lot much interesting",
      "d": "so more interesting",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Much/far/ rather/a little/a bit/ a lot + adj: to emphasize adj \n- Comparative: adj + er (short adj)/ more adj (long adj) ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "9",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is ___ to work out a plan than to carry it out.",
      "a": "easier",
      "b": "easy",
      "c": "more easily",
      "d": "easily",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Comparative: adj + er (short adj)/ more adj (long adj) \n- Easy is short adj ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "9",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kevin plays badminton badly. Howard plays even ___.",
      "a": "more badly",
      "b": "badly",
      "c": "worsely",
      "d": "worse",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Comparative: adj + er (short adj)/ more adj (long adj) \n- \"Bad\" is irregular adj: bad- worse- worst ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "9",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}